GEOFF SULLIVAN

THE BUSINESS OF TECHNOLOGY AND THE TECHNOLOGY OF BUSINESS



CONTACT

596 A Wellington St W, Toronto, ON M5V 2X5 geoffrsullivan@gmail.com +1 (514) 349-9809 @sullivg2 geoffsullivan.net

EXPERTISE

Go-to-market strategy

Content strategy

Partnerships / Alliances

Business Development

Cloud infrastructure

Network infrastructure

Blockchain

Enterprise, Service Provider

CERTIFICATIONS

Certified ScrumMaster®, Scrum Alliance, 2016-2018

Pragmatic Marketing Certified - Level Two (PMC-II)

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Commerce in

Marketing, Saint Mary's University, 2007-2011

SNAPSHOT

I am a technology marketer and cloud infrastructure specialist who is fascinated about the business of technology, and the technology of business. My background is in technology marketing, sales, business development, channel partners, and technical consulting as well as some ongoing entrepreneurial endeavors. This experience has given me a unique perspective on the enterprise and service provider technology ecosystem where now, community, "openness" and APIs are such critical components. I'm interested in how technology impacts business and my speciality is bringing highly technical, disruptive products and services to market.

EXPERIENCE

Head of Marketing - Americas International

Juniper Networks, Canada, Caribbean & Latin America

Jan 2017 - Present

I was promoted to lead a team of marketers who are focused on growing Juniper's enterprise and service provider business in Canada, and the highly strategic Caribbean and Latin America markets - a \$160 million dollar business for Juniper.

- Implemented a "start from scratch" marketing strategy to analyze marketing spend and ROI on activities in the Americas International regions with a focus on pipeline generation and return on investment
- Managed a marketing opex budget of over \$500,000
- Hand selected to collaborate, contribute and prepare Juniper's global go-to-market strategy for the global service provider vertical for presentation to the board of directors
- Presented at Juniper's major customer event, NXTWORK in Las Vegas

Marketing Manager - Content, Strategy & Thought Leadership

Juniper Networks, North America & CALA

Jan 2017 - June 2018

I was promoted to take on this new role within Juniper's Americas Field Marketing organization to provide content direction and strategy to support all pipeline activities from digital demand and top of funnel creation through sales achievement.

- Worked cross functionally with product line management, product marketing and sales to
 ensure that Juniper's messaging is effectively landing in the field support Juniper sellers
 and partners.
- Provide oversight to support the development, launch and management of marketing campaigns.
 - 2018 Enterprise Multi Cloud Campaign, 2018 Service Provider Transformation Campaign and 2018 Security Campaign Architected Juniper's T2/T3 service provider go-to-market strategy in the Americas
- Provide oversight to support new product and solution launches
 - Provide direction and support for joint-offering launches with service provider and cloud partners (Azure and AWS marketplace content strategy for vMX and vSRX platforms, vSRX/NFX250 for AT&T, Verizon, Bell.)
 - Architected a campaign to build pipeline for SkyATP's deployment in Canada
- Craft thought leadership presentation content for global and regional industry events, executive briefing meetings and customer Innovation Days.
 - Leveraged experts in Cognitive Neuroscience to create and deliver memorable and actionable messages for Juniper's prospects and customers

Head of Marketing - Canada

Juniper Networks, Canada

Dec 2016 - Jan 2017

I lead Enterprise/Commercial and Channel marketing for Juniper Networks in Canada.

- Managed a + \$1 million combined marketing opex and MDF budget
- Managed two major service provider "sell through" marketing partner relationships (Bell and TELUS)
- Initiated a special project to deploy Juniper's cloud based anti-malware SaaS product to a Canadian cloud region to satisfy data residency requirements..

INDUSTRY COURSEWORK Red Hat Sales Engineer

(laaS)

Red Hat Sales Specialist (IaaS)

Red Hat Sales Engineer -Cloud Management

DevOps Essentials - Linux Academy

AWS Technical Professional

AWS Business Professional

FXTRAS

Community Ambassador -Tungsten Fabric

Toronto Open Source Networking Meetup -Co-founder and organizer

Waterloo Codefest Hackathon - Judge

OpenStack Day Canada -Organizing Committee Member & master of ceremony

Construction Association of NS - Technology and Innovation Committee Member

Ongoing Freelance & Entrepreneurial Work

Various Organizations, Global

2015 - Present

In my personal time i've taken on dozens of interesting freelance projects in my pursuit of continuous learning. Most of these projects have been writing engagements, web design, qo-to-market & technical strategy.

- Technical Advisor <u>Ammeris</u>
- Partner, advisor, part-time data centre technician and cloud architect <u>Cloud-A</u>
- Co-founder <u>cryptonoob.club</u> A cryptocurrency mining cooperative we've built for friends and family
- Technical Contributor & Product Testing FIXATE.IO.
- Blogger- Various online publications including: 1CloudRoad, Hustle & Grind, Cloud 66, OpenContrail.org, Red Hat, The Crypto Noob Club, Crypto Canucks and more...

Cloud Practice Lead

MOBIA Technology Innovations, Montreal, QC

Nov 2015 - Dec 2016

Responsible for building and operating MOBIA's new cloud consulting practice. Provide thought leadership for MOBIA, analyze new cloud technologies and trends, design service and product offerings. Responsible for the overall practice go-to-market strategy, business development, planning, management and project delivery oversight.

- Won five year bid for designing and building Bell Canada's Network 3.0 initiative on OpenStack.
- Retired FY16 Sales Quota in Q2
- Overhauled MOBIA's digital strategy with the launch of MOBIA.io
- Initiated and built a symbiotic partnership and go-to-market strategy with Red Hat focused on OpenStack, OpenShift, Ansible and JBoss. Achieved Advanced Business Partner status in just 4 months.

Director of Growth

Cloud-A, Halifax, NS

Nov 2014 - Nov 2015

I was the first hire Canada's first OpenStack-powered public cloud. I managed and drove all aspects of Cloud-A's pursuit of monthly recurring revenue including new business development, partnerships, technology integrations and marketing initiatives.

- Achieved 300% YoY revenue growth
- Developed and managed a channel partner strategy
- Successfully designed and executed all marketing campaigns
- Active in all aspects of product development
- Authored technical and marketing content including several well received whitepapers
- Took on operational tasks including budgeting and back office management

Account Manager

Dymaxion Research Limited, Halifax, NS

Dec 2012 - Nov 2014

Maintain and expand current client relationships as well new business development.

- Represent Dymaxion's product and service offering to client base and develop client solutions that show true value
- Create and strengthen relationships with channel partners; both manufacturing and distribution
- Provide input to management on product/service portfolio and corporate strategy
- Acted as project manager for client implementation projects

Sales Executive, US Major Accounts

Xerox Canada, Dartmouth, NS

Dec 2011 - Nov 2012

Drive revenue and effectively manage internal and external customer relationships by applying a consultative approach to analyzing customer needs and requirements

 Managed a national territory that included McKesson, Applied Materials, Southern Company and Ace Insurance